Remember to adjust the particle diameter accordingly.
Because I reduced the particle diameter of the pants.
Is it like changing the magic?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
No, right?
In fact, if you follow this step,
it will be the final look in the video.
And then the hat, in the previous episode,
the previous episode or the previous two episodes,
there is a live broadcast of making hats in the previous two episodes.
Not hard.
Not hard, everyone.
I personally think the final effect is okay.
You can also go to next Monday.
When I post this video,
follow me.
You can follow this video and these accessories to make the suit.
Of course, if you have a limited edition of this suit paper,
you can draw directly on it.
Or go to our.
I'll re-cut a software.
Or we can go back to us.
Say it again.
Or you can find it in the modular configuration.
Men Jacket
Single
Because of
In the MV, we can see that there are basically two single-line buttons.
Then double click, double click, so that we can import the ready-to-use suit.
This is a ready-to-use suit.
Hmm, it's not hard. Do you have any problems with MD?
Hmm, it's not hard, it's not hard.
I should release the video next Monday.
Hey, I don't know if you have found this menu.
I actually put two cards here.
Then I will post it on my website.
Then I want to say that I want to make a magician effect.
Hmm, yes, if you want to make a button, I think you need to change some methods.
If the button is always closed, it will be very influential.
We will cancel it and remember it.
Then wait for it to be covered and remember it.
MD starts a specific spell, it feels quite difficult.
Yes, that's right.
Because sometimes, if you must have some, to be honest, if you must have some very specific spells,
For example, you must have a very vertical spell here.
First of all, if you want to add a spell here, you actually need to know the starting point of this spell.
For example, this point is the end point, the bottom two points, then you should make a triangle here.
But in real life, after you make a triangle, this line will be blocked.
This shape is not the same as what you originally imagined.
You may need to add some nails next to it.
At this time, I think you may just go directly to carving.
Because our software is in the game industry, basically a lot of game companies are using our software.
What about them?
In general, a lot of game companies are using our software.
Yes, a lot of game companies are using our software.
In general, they usually start with a big shape first, because it takes a long time to start with a big shape in Marvel's Designer.
If you must have some simple spells, or some very specific spells, you have to go to ZB and do some detailed sketching.
If you do animation calculation with a physical chain, I personally think it is not very convenient.
Just do the kind of animation that you have to pull the chain out.
Because the chain is so long that it will affect the line.
Because the chain has an action that needs to be pulled out.
I don't know whether you can understand me.
And then when the line is modified, it will affect your animation recording.
You may not have the animation you recorded before.
So at the moment, I don't recommend you to do this kind of animation with a physical chain in Marvelous 3D.
About the animation related content, you can take a look at the animation entry or animation optimization videos I made before.
If you have any questions, please feel free to ask them in the comment section below.
Do you have any questions?
Yes, it's really hard to make a physical chain.
It's also because of what my friend said about dragging socks.
Especially for socks,
In Marvelous 3D,
the way of making socks is different from the way people actually wear socks.
Because people's skin is flexible.
But in Marvelous 3D,
there are still no flexible skin settings in our software.
In the case of this setting,
there is no such setting.
The skin can't really do it in real life.
It's a bit difficult.
I think...
This suit...
Actually...
If we look at it...
Let me show you what I did at the beginning.
Wait a minute.
Let me show you.
When you stand upright,
you can't really feel the wrinkle effect of this suit.
But...
You have to make it clear.
This is just an A pose.
And there is no extra material or
Because I pulled it out to show it off at the end.
You see, the difference is actually quite big.
Because you added a...
Some movement of the legs.
These...
These wrinkles.
You can clearly feel the texture of the pants.
And some of his suit.
Right?
So everyone must know.
If you just do...
First of all, if you are a user who is very interested in AMD,
I am very grateful to you.
Just so interested in our software.
If you are a personal user,
Usually,
Some of the works produced by yourself,
Or say you like it.
Or you are a student.
Then I think you can use all kinds of poses.
To do different clothing effects.
As long as you do it.
Just a mirror.
Because when you do a mirror,
Usually you will choose some special effects.
Because if you do an A pose,
It doesn't have these wrinkles.
Uh,
We talked about it in the video of the wrinkle class.
You can completely change the movement of your legs.
For example,
The movement of your legs.
Let your whole body lean forward.
Or let your feet bend a little.
Then you can use this shape optimization function.
To solidify these wrinkles.
Um.
Yes.
What I mean is,
For example,
You have some...
Just a lot of users.
When you do an A pose,
There are a lot of wrinkles.
You can use these to solidify the wrinkles.
Then,
Let this model match the movements of some characters.
Right?
Because you can't say that every...
Most games can't do it.
You can't do it at the same time.
It must be a lot of computing.
It must not work.
It must be a set of magic tricks.
It's normal, right?
If that's the case,
You have to think differently.
If most of the moves are..
All in one stroke.
Then you should find...
The most common running posture.
It...
It allows you to make a slope...
On the A pose.
But you can change it.
This running posture.
Come in, then choose the shape optimization.
After the shape optimization,
Come back to...
This A pose.
In this way,
Its creases are still there.
I have told you before, for example, I have this model now, right?
I may have some cards before I calculate it.
For example, let me take a look.
Because there are more panels.
For example, you can give it a leg lift.
Of course, you have to be a little slower when you lift it.
Don't lift it too much at once.
If you lift it too much at once, this panel will be easy to pass through.
Then wait for it to be well simulated.
First of all, my pants are not tight pants.
If you are a tight pants,
it should be pleated here.
Let me show you another panel.
In fact, I have mentioned the pleating class before.
For example, I will make a line-shaped pants for it now.
Wait a moment.
Because the latest version,
we have to change the interface.
So sometimes when you cut this interface,
it will be a little lagged.
For example, I put a pair of pants in now.
Then many times,
it will ask you to make a pleating under this pose.
Right?
If that's the case,
you can give it a leg lift.
Just bend it a little bit.
Then here too.
Bend it a little bit.
In fact, at this time,
you will already have some pleating.
Then there is such a pleating.
First of all,
because I haven't added a belt to it now.
Right?
And then in the layout,
it has some pleating.
Then we can use,
first of all, you can use this segmental shape optimization.
Oh, don't choose frozen.
Choose segmental shape optimization.
Then you put this posture
back to
this position.
Normal A pose.
Ah.
After that,
in fact, the pleating here will be retained.
Do you understand?
I often
choose in different
movements.
In fact, my A pose
is just for wearing clothes.
I usually choose
to try it under different angles.
Until I feel that
this pleating can still be used.
When the shape is not bad,
I will save this part of the pleating.
Just use this kind of
selection grid tool.
Just choose and then select the shape optimization.
Just keep this part of the pleating.
You can see.
Although I change the position of this pleating,
the pleating it should have is still there.
Including the cloth here.
There is one more point.
In the early stage of this live broadcast today,
I told everyone that you must
make it clear.
No matter your pants.
For example, the pants.
No matter how loose your bottom is.
If you want to have some
obvious pleats here.
Especially the hip here.
It's still tight.
It's easy to have pleats.
Because it needs to be strong.
It's easy to have these pleats.
Because the pleats are either a pile of cloth.
Or the pleats are made by force.
Of course, the specific situation.
Specific analysis.
You can also use it like me.
You can see.
Like this side.
I'm going to bend my feet.
Bend your knees.
And some pleats.
And then use this part of the shape optimization.
To optimize these pleats.
Haha.
I probably
have heard this before.
Do you guys have any questions
about using Marvelous Designer?
Actually,
after changing the movement,
I think the shape of the pants is not bad.
I think it's actually the same.
If you are doing it yourself.
If you are doing some modeling.
You can totally choose this.
It's more able to show
some of the texture movements.
Because I actually used this movement.
I tried two movements.
The original movement.
I don't think the pleats look good.
So I changed to another one.
The current movement.
Yes.
Because.
In fact, in the game.
With you completely.
This reality.
The result.
There are still some differences.
Because in real life.
There are some people.
In the game.
It's just.
It's not suitable.
So it's normal.
Okay.
Women's clothing tutorial.
I used to have a lot of episodes.
Before.
People often ask me why I don't do men's makeup.
Now.
Ask me why I don't have women's makeup.
Most of the videos I made before
were all about women's makeup.
Haha.
If you want to watch.
For example.
Hana's clothing.
If you are a beginner.
I recommend you to watch.
Hanfu.
And how to change a T-shirt.
Into a dress.
They are all good.
Men's makeup.
Mainly because I think men's makeup.
Um.
Many of them are.
For example.
Um.
It doesn't have any strong characteristics.
For women.
For example, women's dress.
Is a kind.
For men.
In fact, this suit.
I want to take advantage of the popularity.
And then I did it.
Because I feel that we are not systematic.
Explain to everyone.
Um.
How to do these effects.
So today.
This live broadcast is also.
The broadcast time is relatively long.
I want to make it clear to you.
These are just these.
How do you adjust according to the size of your model.
And then how to fix it.
Just doing it.
Problems encountered when doing a multi-layer structure.
So.
And then there's the suit.
These special effects of the suit.
For example.
How to do these.
In fact, a lot of times.
Let me show you this.
The actual version.
You will soon understand.
What this is like.
It's just that there's no such reference.
Right?
Ah.
For example.
Like this.
You actually see the project file I made.
You know.
Oh.
This is actually like this.
Fold in.
And then there's one in the middle.
In fact, it's equivalent to a fold.
It's just that it's in the clothing.
This professional terminology.
It's called bad.
I actually think this color match is pretty good.
I actually made two colors.
One is black.
One is brown.
In the end, I think the brown one is still the brown one.
This suit is better.
The black suit is a bit unclear.
It's still good.
I think this is good.
Then, thanks for the support.
For everyone who supports the software.
I watched the live stream for so long.
I've been live streaming for a long time today.
I've been live streaming for almost four hours.
We have the recording.
We have the recording today.
We have it written in the left corner.
We have a recording every time we live stream.
Don't worry.
This video will be uploaded later.
This video will be uploaded next Monday.
Do you have any questions?
Questions about Marvelous Designer?
You can add our QQ group or follow our Bilibili account.
It will automatically send you our latest QQ group account and password.
Let's see what time it is now.
Let's end at 11.3.
There are 4 minutes left.
Do you have anything else you want to talk about?
There will be a recording.
Or do you have any educational videos you want to see?
But actually, I usually watch these educational videos and livestreams in groups.
And I force you to reply to them.
Just...
I usually watch them.
Including the suit I'm wearing this time.
Actually, it's not to warm up.
It's just...
It's not...
Ah! I don't even cut my videos.
I don't know how to cut them.
Why do I have to cut them?
It can't be.
I'm very real.
I don't know how to cut my videos.
I might cut the video of me going to the bathroom in the middle.
But that video is very short.
Really?
Then do you think my livestream is clear?
I think my livestream has been very clear this time.
Except for the second half.
Because there are many repetitive steps in the second half.
And if you don't know much about this livestream,
you can come to our group and ask me.
From Monday to Friday, from 9pm to 6pm, I'm usually there.
It's just that the reply is fast...
Or slow.
Because sometimes when I'm busy, I might not reply in a second.
But I usually reply when I see a problem.
I also hope that after you join our group, you can...
You can help each other more actively.
This way, we can...
We can learn together.
Right?
When I first saw Topp...
I don't know.
Topp seems to be in the update plan.
Because it will optimize the smart topp later.
Because the smart topp still...
There are still some places that need to be optimized.
For example, like the pool.
These.
We have this in...
In the updated list.
Because there are smart topps now.
And this...
In Chinese, it's called support topp points.
Do we have these?
And then it should be based on these...
Some optimization of smart topp and support topp points.
Because...
I think...
Actually, I think smart topp is already quite useful.
In the future, it should be.
Can't exceed 20 modifiers.
Yes.
Yeah.
Loosening this is true.
Because a lot of friends said they wanted that...
Loosening this function.
Yeah.
So I've mentioned this.
Functional development needs.
But...
In actual development...
Maybe it takes some time.
Can we increase the number of modifiers?
For now, I don't think we can.
It won't work if it's online.
20 is a bit less.
Then you can add more.
You don't have to choose too many at once.
This...
This can...
Draw a lot of areas on a board.
Just add them little by little.
Hehe.
Okay.
Hmm.
If I have a chance in the future,
I can inform you a little bit.
Because I know that right now,
there's a function that's quite useful.
In...
The next version...
I have to try it.
Is there a display on the side? No, it's not, you said there would be a few more points, right?
That's the support top point, it will add points along the position of the sewing line, if you have a top on the other side.
If you don't have any questions, we can continue to talk about the content in the QQ group.
Of course, I recommend that you add more QQ groups.
It's not bad to add a group, right?
If you think it's convenient for everyone to chat,
you can ask in the QQ group if you have any questions.
You can also take a look at what everyone is talking about.
Because we still have a lot of technical support and questions every day.
Thank you for your support.
There will be replays, there will be replays.
Next time, I'm going to change the title of our live broadcast to
There will be replays.
No, everyone is not all in the dark.
No one is all in the dark.
No, no.
We are all communicating seriously.
Are you in the first group?
There are more children and new friends in the second group.
The frequency of technical support in the second group is a little higher.
Well, that's it for today.
That's it.
Thank you for your support.
That's the end of our content today.
Welcome to follow our live broadcast room.
Follow our Bilibili account.